export const data = [
    {
        question:"What is the full form of OSI?",
        option1:"optical service implementation",
        option2:"open service Internet",
        option3:"open system interconnection",
        option4:"operating system interface",
        ans:3,
    },
    {
        question:"How many layers are there in the ISO OSI reference model?",
        option1:"7",
        option2:"4",
        option3:"5",
        option4:"6",
        ans:1,
    },
    {
        question:"Which one of the following is not a function of network layer?",
        option1:"congestion control",
        option2:"error control",
        option3:"routing",
        option4:"inter-networking",
        ans:2,
    },

    {
        question:"Which topology requires a multipoint connection?",
        option1:"Ring",
        option2:"Bus",
        option3:"Star",
        option4:"Mesh",
        ans:2,
    },

    {
        question:" What was the name of the first network?",
        option1:"ASAPNET",
        option2:"ARPANET",
        option3:"CNNET",
        option4:"NSFNET",
        ans:2,
    },
    {
        question:"Which layer provides the services to user?",
        option1:"physical layer",
        option2:"presentation layer",
        option3:"session layer",
        option4:"application layer",
        ans:4,
    },
    {
        question:"The HTTP request message is sent in _________ part of three-way handshake.",
        option1:"First",
        option2:"Second",
        option3:"Third",
        option4:"Fourth",
        ans:3,
    },
    
    {
        question:"Two broad categories of congestion control are",
        option1:"Open-loop and Closed-loop",
        option2:"Open-control and Closed-control",
        option3:"Active control and Passive control",
        option4:" Active loop and Passive loop",
        ans:1,
    },

    {
        question:"Discarding policy is mainly done by _______",
        option1:"Sender",
        option2:"Reciever",
        option3:"Router",
        option4:"Switch",
        ans:3,
    },

    {
        question:"Backpressure technique can be applied only to _______",
        option1:"Congestion networks",
        option2:"Closed circuit networks",
        option3:"Open circuit networks",
        option4:"Virtual circuit networks",
        ans:3,
    },


    

];